Guide to the Randolph Linsly Simpson African-American Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize
  - Unknown Photographer, Group of Cooks and Bakers (in Series I), circa 1863 (Box 48, Folder 1194)
  - Unknown photographer, Annapolis Cemetery, group of grave diggers with shovels (in Series I), circa 1870 (Box 48, Folder 1195)
  - R.R. Morris, Greenwood, SC, Bales of cotton at freight warehouse (in Series I), circa 1867 (Box 48, Folder 1196)
  - Unknown photographer, Half a dozen white men in military uniform, saluting black man (in Series I), circa 1885 (Box 48, Folder 1197)
  - Leopold, New Haven, CT, Wilkins Guard, Co. A. 5th Battalion (in Series I), 1907 (Box 48, Folder 1198)
  - Leopold, New Haven, CT, Wilkins Guard, Co. A. 5th Battalion (in Series I), 1907 (Box 48, Folder 1199)
  - Leopold, New Haven, CT, Military group portrait, "New Haven Grays." (in Series I), 1902 (Box 48, Folder 1200)
  - Royal Photo Co., Lou.(isville) KY, Group portrait: National Negro Business League (in Series I), 1909 August (Box 48, Folder 1201)
  - Unknown photographer, Group of workmen outside motor repair shop (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 48, Folder 1202)
  - Empire Photo Pub. Co., New York, View of Golf Livery Stables (in Series I), circa 1916 (Box 48, Folder 1203)
  - Commercial Photo Co., New York, Group of workers stand in front of building (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 48, Folder 1204)
  - Large group of men, most in uniform (in Series I), 1903 (Box 48, Folder 1205)
  - Fowler, Philadelphia, Full length seated portrait Kelsey Keyes (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 48, Folder 1206)
  - Unknown photographer, portrait of young man with long, drooping moustache (in Series I), circa 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1207)
  - Underwood & Underwood, New York, Young boy in sailor suit (in Series I), circa 1935 (Box 48, Folder 1208)
  - Underwood & Underwood, New York, Portrait of "Billie 'Buckwheat' Thomas" (in Series I), undated (Box 48, Folder 1209)
  - Unknown photographer, Track and Field Team of the Wilkins Guard (in Series I), circa 1910 (Box 48, Folder 1210)
  - Unknown photographer, Group portrait; sailors in "whites" (in Series I), 1944 (Box 48, Folder 1211)
  - Creedman, Cambridge (MA), School group: students with teachers at center (in Series I), 1923 (Box 48, Folder 1212)
  - Unknown photographer, View of large clapboard church with minister (in Series I), undated (Box 48, Folder 1213)
  - McKay, Akron, OH, Family group standing in front of house (in Series I), undated (Box 49, Folder 1214)
  - Millers, Sabina, Ohio, School group with teacher on concrete steps (in Series I), circa 1905 (Box 49, Folder 1215)
  - Crown Studio, Bridgeport, CT, Junior High Graduating Class (in Series I), 1922 (Box 49, Folder 1216)
  - Unknown photographer, Workers in tunnel with picks and shovels (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1217)
  - Unknown photographer, Display booth with chefs and servers at counter (in Series I), undated (Box 49, Folder 1218)
  - Ralph Harris & Co., Boston, Three children in two-wheeled donkey cart (in Series I), circa 1910 (Box 49, Folder 1219)
  - Hobby Studio, New York, Group portrait of a baseball team (in Series I), circa 1914 (Box 49, Folder 1220)
  - Jim Predmore, Everett, NM, Group portrait of postmen (in Series I), 1909 (Box 49, Folder 1221)
  - Unknown photographer, Group of six snapshots labeled: "The Darkest Side of College Life." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1222)
  - Unknown photographer, Group of men in formal attire (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 49, Folder 1223)
  - Unknown photographer, "Harvesting Rice, Louisiana, U.S." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1224)
  - Unknown photographer, "Baling Cotton, Arkansas." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1225)
  - Unknown photographer, "Picking Cotton, Arkansas." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1226)
  - Unknown photographer, "Harvesting Flax, Washington." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1227)
  - Unknown photographer, "Cotton Gins, Arkansas." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1228)
  - Unknown photographer, "Baling Cotton, Arkansas." (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1229)
  - Unknown photographer, Public square in Birmingham filled with farmers (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder 1230)
  - Unknown photographer, Co. Comd'r. E. W. Marold Eni (in Series I), 1953 November 3 (Box 49, Folder 1231)
  - Unknown Photographer, Co. Comd'r. E. W. Marold Eni (in Series I), 1954 April 12 (Box 49, Folder 1232)
  - Bonneville, del. et sculp., "Toussaint L'Ouverture" (in Series I), circa 1815 (Box 49, Folder 1233)
  - Bl. Hofel, sc. Wein bey S.A. Steiner und Comp., "Heinrich I, König von Haiti" (in Series I), circa 1820 (Box 49, Folder 1234)
  - Painted by Chappel; Engraved by Phillibrown, "Washington Family at Mount Vernon" (in Series I), circa 1856 (Box 49, Folder 1235)
  - Designed by F.O.C. Darley, "Last Words of Captain Nathan Hale..." (in Series I), 1858 (Box 50, Folder 1236)
  - N. Currier, New York, "Death of Washington, Dec. 14, A.D. 1799" (in Series I), circa 1864 (Box 50, Folder 1237)
  - V. Berne Bellecour(?), "Waiting for the Attack" (in Series I), undated (Box 50, Folder 1238)
  - FAS, Made in U.S.A., "Home Sweet Home" (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 50, Folder 1239)
  - Arthur Szyk, Paris, "Washington Crossing the Delaware" (in Series I), 1931 (Box 50, Folder 1240)
  - Harper's Weekly cover, bust portrait of Frederick Douglass (in Series I), 1883 (Box 50, Folder 1241)
  - Winslow Homer for Harper's Weekly, "Expulsion of Negroes and Abolitionists from Fremont's Temple..." (in Series I), 1860 (Box 50, Folder 1242)
  - Unknown photographer, Group portrait of an all male (possibly) choral group (in Series I), circa 1900 (Box 50, Folder 1243)
  - Unknown photographer, Military banquet in a drill hall (in Series I), 1893 July 6 (Box 50, Folder 1244)
  - Unknown printer, "Hear our War Heroes", Flyer (in Series II), undated (Box 50, Folder 1245)
  - Press of Wynkoop & Hallenbeck, New York, Key to the engraving entitled "The Triumph of Freedom Over Slavery" (in Series II), 1865 (Box 50, Folder 1246)
  - Unknown Photographer, Two chefs in a kitchen (in Series I), undated (Box 50, Folder 1247)
  - Vitagraph, Inc., Publicity photograph: Bette Davis in Jezebel Brent (in Series I), 1938 (Box 50, Folder 1248)
  - G.& W. Endicott, New York, NY, Lithograph from a daguerreotype by Plumbe (in Series II), circa 1845 (Box 50, Folder 1249)
  - S.H. Gimber, Engraver, New York, "Immediate Emancipation in the West Indies..." (in Series II), circa 1838 (Box 50, Folder 1250)
  - Studio unknown, Full length portrait, little girl with braids in polka dot dress (in Series I), circa 1870 (Box 51, Folder 1251)
  - Studio unknown, Oval bust portrait of a man in four piece suit and bow tie (in Series I), circa 1875 (Box 51, Folder 1252)
  - Unknown photographer, Full length bubble portrait, lady seated on stool (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 52, Folder 1253)
  - Unknown photographer, Full length group portrait, double wedding group (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 52, Folder 1254)
  - E. Powell, New York, "Anti-Slavery Constitutional Amendment Picture" (in Series I), 1863 (Box 52, Folder 1255)
  - Studio unknown, Young man standing with hand on chair (in Series I), circa 1870 (Box 53)
  - Pach, New York, Half-length portrait of "Professor Charlie"; Cameo portrait of Mary Ann Wolker (in Series I), 1883 (Box 54, Folder 1256)
    Item #238.1 and #238.2
  - Ben Dann, Baltimore, MD, Full length portrait, man standing; holds his hat in right hand (in Series I), circa 1867 (Box 54, Folder 1257)
  - Unknown photographer, Street Scene: unhitched railroad car at left (in Series I), 1880 (Box 54, Folder 1258)
  - Unknown photographer, Advertisement poster for C.W. Slagle & Co. (in Series I), circa 1880 (Box 54, Folder 1259)
  - Unknown photographer, Cotton Gin: tin-sided building (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 54, Folder 1260)
  - Unknown photographer, A dozen wagons full of raw, unprocessed cotton (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 54, Folder 1261)
  - Donnelly Studio, New Haven, CT, Family portrait (in Series I), circa 1898 (Box 54, Folder 1262)
  - G. Waldon Smith, Boston, MA, Group portrait: 25 male athletes (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 54, Folder 1263)
  - Gilbert's Studio, Philadelphia, PA, University of Pennsylvania, Dr. Alfred Stengel (in Series I), circa 1905 (Box 54, Folder 1264)
  - Purdy, Boston, MA, Boston Latin: group portrait (in Series I), 1906 (Box 54, Folder 1265)
  - Randall, Group of young women on steps of institutional building (in Series I), circa 1909 (Box 54, Folder 1266)
  - Unknown photographer, Oval bust length portrait of Paul Lawrence Dunbar (in Series I), circa 1900 (Box 54, Folder 1267)
  - Fellowcrafts Photo Shop, Albany, NY, Large group portrait of lodge members (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1268)
  - Unknown photographer, View from orchestra, overlooking orchestra pit (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 55, Folder 1269)
  - Unknown photographer, Company Christmas Party (in Series I), circa 1925 (Box 55, Folder 1270)
  - Stringer's Studio, Windber, PA, Group portrait of a baseball team (in Series I), circa 1930 (Box 55, Folder 1271)
  - Unknown photographer, Large group seated in sand before sea wall (in Series I), 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1272)
  - John G. Hemmer, Pinehurst, NC, Bullock wagon, with southern pines in background (in Series I), 1928 (Box 55, Folder 1273)
  - Altman, New Haven, CT, Group portrait: students photographed before entrance of Ivy Street School (in Series I), 1925 (Box 55, Folder 1274)
  - Crosby, New Haven, Group portrait of football team with coaches (in Series I), 1936 (Box 55, Folder 1275)
  - Unknown photographer, Five photographs of the Dartmouth football team of 1920 (in Series I) (Box 55, Folder 1276)
  - Drew B. Peters, Photography Center, "Awarding of Prizes to Boy Scouts..." (in Series I), 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1277)
  - Drew B. Peters, Photography, An album page with a total of 9 photographs (in Series I), 1920 (Box 55, Folder 1278)
  - Currier & Ives, 125 Nassau Street, "The Washington Family" (in Series I), circa 1850 (Box 55, Folder 1279)
  - Currier & Ives, New York, NY, "The Washington Family" (in Series I), 1867 (Box 55, Folder 1280)
  - Currier and Ives, New York, NY, "The Colored Beauty" (in Series I), 1878 (Box 55, Folder 1281)
  - After the painting by John Trumbull; T.W. Strong, NY, "Battle at Bunker's Hill" (in Series I), undated (Box 55, Folder 1282)
  - M. Lynch, "Old Black Joe" (in Series I), 1903 (Box 55, Folder 1283)
  - B.W. Brittain, no location, "The Dawn of Hope" (in Series I), 1918 (Box 55, Folder 1284)
  - Currier and Ives, New York, Political cartoon: "Practical Illustration of the Fugitive Slave Law" (in Series I), 1852 (Box 55, Folder 1285)
  - Greenway and Brown, Printers, Philadelphia, PA, Provisional Commission Certificate for James Clark Stockton (in Series II), 1864 March 26 (Box 55, Folder 1286)
  - B.F.K. Rives, Women's Suffrage Association Convention, Large elegantly dressed crowd (in Series I), 1883 (Box 55, Folder 1287)
  - Unknown photographer, New York State, Regimental photograph of mostly artillerymen (in Series I), circa 1910 (Box 55, Folder 1288)
  - Edward Edwin, Philadelphia, [PA], "Portrait of Martha Washington, her daughter and William Lee" (in Series II), circa 1790 (Box 55, Folder 1289)
  - Royal Photo Co., Louisville, KY, "Training School for Chaplains and Approved Chaplain Candidates" (in Series I), circa 1918 (Box 55, Folder 1290)
  - Lithograph by F. Ratellier, New York, "Camp of the 13th Regt., Conn. Vols..." (in Series II), 1863 (Box 55, Folder 1291)
  - Alexander Gardner, Washington, D.C., "Scene in Pleasant Valley Maryland..." (in Series I), 1862 October (Box 55, Folder 1292)
  - Randall, [New Haven, CT], School group seated outside on school steps (in Series I), circa 1918 (Box 55, Folder 1293)
  - Winslow Homer, "A Shell in the Rebel Trenches" (in Series II), 1863 January 17 (Box 55, Folder 1294)
  - Studio unknown, Full length double portrait, two soldiers in uniform (in Series I), circa 1865 (Box 56)
  - J. H. Tarbell, Asheville, N.C., Four children by a board fence, two white, two black, 1897 (Box 57, Folder 1295)
  - Studio unknown, Bust portrait of John Enos in suit (in Series I), 1879 (Box 57, Folder 1296)
  - Unknown photographer, Group of Civil War officers and civilians (in Series I), circa 1863 (Box 58, Folder 1297)
  - Unknown photographer, Six men in a kitchen tent (in Series I), circa 1880 (Box 58, Folder 1298)
  - Unknown photographer, Formal graduation group portrait of young men and women (in Series I), circa 1898 (Box 58, Folder 1299)
  - Underwood & Underwood, Regimental portrait; infantry battalion on dress parade (in Series I), 1905 (Box 58, Folder 1300)
  - Carl [?], Jefferson City, Group portrait, string band (in Series I), circa 1910 (Box 58, Folder 1301)
  - San Fl[?] Company, Philadelphia, PA, Group portrait: Knights Templar Band of Harrisburg, PA (in Series I), 1915 (Box 58, Folder 1302)
  - Unknown photographer, Allentown, PA, Group portrait of Allentown football team (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 58, Folder 1303)
  - Unknown photographer, Large group photo of men and women in military dress (in Series I), 1920 (Box 58, Folder 1304)
  - Townsend, New York, Full length standing portrait of Bill, "Bojangles" Robinson (in Series I), 1931 (Box 58, Folder 1305)
  - Coovert, Memphis, Tenn., Cotton being weighed before being loaded into wagons (in Series I), 1931 (Box 58, Folder 1306)
  - Unknown photographer, Full length portrait of Melvin (in Series I), circa 1903 (Box 58, Folder 1307)
  - Unknown photographer, "The Keene White Sox Baseball Team, 1923-24." (in Series I), 1924 (Box 58, Folder 1308)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, "Harvesting Peanuts, Building the Stack." (in Series I), circa 1950 (Box 58, Folder 1309)
  - David Hughes, Niagara Falls, NY, Close-up of man with capped teeth (in Series I), circa 1944 (Box 58, Folder 1310)
  - Philippe Halsman, New York, NY, Duke Ellington in recording studio conducting band (in Series I), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 1311)
  - Philippe Halsman, New York, NY, Duke Ellington in recording studio instructing musicians (in Series I), 1967 (Box 58, Folder 1312)
  - Unknown photographer, Group Portrait of World War II Army unit (in Series I), circa 1944 (Box 58, Folder 1313)
  - Unknown photographer, Full length formal portrait, William Frank Roach (in Series I), 1918 (Box 59, Folder 1314)
  - Peint par L. Le Paon, "Liberté" in cartouche in center of title (in Series I), 1781 (Box 59, Folder 1315)
  - H.W. Herriok, Del.; J.W. Watts, Sc.,"Reading the Emancipation Proclamation:" (in Series I), 1864 (Box 59, Folder 1316)
  - From the original portrait by E.D. Marchant, "Abraham Lincoln, President of the United States." (in Series I), 1864 (Box 59, Folder 1317)
  - Paris, L. Turgis, "St. Francis Xavier, Apostle of the Indies" (in Series I), circa 1840 (Box 59, Folder 1318)
  - E. Forbes, "The Sanctuary" (in Series I), 1876 (Box 59, Folder 1319)
  - T.W. Wood, Elderly man stands wrapped in quilt (in Series I), 1883 (Box 59, Folder 1320)
  - Elizabeth O'Neill Verner, "Mom Lydia" (in Series I), circa 1930 (Box 59, Folder 1321)
  - After William Sidney Mount, by Cowdry and Williams, "The Power of Music" (in Series I), circa 1853 (Box 59, Folder 1322)
  - E.G. Renesch, Chicago, [IL], World War I poster: Lincoln and Emancipation Proclamation references (in Series I), 1918 (Box 59, Folder 1323)
  - E.G. Renesch, Chicago, [IL], "Colored Man is No Slacker:" World War I poster (in Series I), 1918 (Box 59, Folder 1324)
  - E. G. Renesch, Chicago, [IL], "True Blue:" World War I poster (in Series I), 1919 (Box 59, Folder 1325)
  - Winslow Homer for Harper's Weekly, "Pay Day; A Descent on the Sutler..." (in Series I), 1863 (Box 59, Folder 1326)
  - S. Begg, "Primate and Negro Preacher...." (in Series I), 1904 October 15 (Box 59, Folder 1327)
  - Richard H. K. Fox, Full length formal portrait, of boxer, "George Dixon" (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 59, Folder 1328)
  - Unknown printer Civilian Conservation Corps, Nine reproduction photographs (in Series II), circa 1938 (Box 59, Folder 1329)
  - Panoramic photographs of headquarters and ordnance companies (in Series II), 1918 (Box 59, Folder 1330)
  - Unknown photographer, Dead man lies in open casket (in Series I), circa 1920 (Box 59, Folder 1331)
  - M.T. Sheahan, Boston, "Young Coons" (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 60, Folder 1332)
  - Empire Photographers, New York, NY, "25048 Thirty Second Annual Spring Conference..." (in Series I), 1957 March 22 (Box 60, Folder 1333)
  - Empire Photographers, New York, NY, "5792 Thirty Third Annual Spring Conference..." (in Series I), 1958 March (Box 60, Folder 1334)
  - Standard Photo Service, "U.P. Law, 1912, Bellevue-Stratford, Phila., Pa." (in Series I), 1931 January 31 (Box 60, Folder 1335)
  - G.V. Buck, Washington, D.C., Group of white men standing on steps of the War Department building (in Series I), 1909 (Box 60, Folder 1336)
  - Falk, Boston, 11th Annual Convention of the A.F.of M. (American Federation of Musicians) (in Series I), 1906 May (Box 60, Folder 1337)
  - Currier & Ives, New York, NY, "John Brown-The Martyr" (in Series II), 1870 (Box 60, Folder 1338)
  - Unknown photographer, Large group portrait of men in college graduation caps and gowns (in Series I), undated (Box 60, Folder 1339)
  - Un-numbered Oversize (in Series I), undated (Box 60, Folder 1340-1343)
  - Cast plaster bust of Booker T. Washington (in Series III), undated (Box 61)
  - Folk art sculpture, bust of a man with mustache (in Series III), undated (Box 61)
  - American Art Company, Portrait of a young man, three quarter length seated (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 62)
  - Reproduction of the bronze high relief sculpture in Boston Commons (in Series I), 1897 (Box 63)
  - Biddle Artistic Photographer, Xenia, OH, Fourteen exterior view photographs of the campus and faculty homes of Wilberforce University (in Series I), 1897 (Box 64)
  - Alexander Gardner, Washington, D.C. "Across the Continent on the Union Pacific Railway..." (in Series I), undated (Box 65)
  - Rintoul & Rockwood, Photographers, New York, "The Old Kentucky Home" (in Series I), 1859 (Box 66)
  - Whitman Studio, Bridgeport, CT, Large group portrait of men and boys in suits in front of a Church (in Series I), 1909 (Box 67)
  - Unknown photographer(s), Montage of 13 photographs. Subjects and personalities of Howard University (in Series I), circa 1915 (Box 68)
  - Patton Studio, Indianapolis, IN, Panoramic group photo of 317th Engineers Band, Camp Sherman, Ohio (in Series I), 1918 May 15 (Box 69)
  - Crosby, Boston, MA, Panoramic group portrait, "1007. Officers and Crew of U.S.S. Little..." (in Series I), 1919 January 15 (Box 70)
  - Crosby, Boston, Mass., "1003. U.S.S. Little, Boston, Mass..." (in Series I), 1919 (Box 71)
  - Thos. A. Slater, Boston, MA, 2nd Sep. Battalion Infantry, Camp Devons, MA (in Series I), 1923 (Box 72)
  - Janis, 117 Gennessee, Atlantic City, Full length standing portrait of an army Lieutenant (in Series I), circa 1917 (Box 73)
  - Baker Art Gallery, Panoramic group portrait, "29th Annual Session of the Divan..." (in Series I), 1928 (Box 74)
  - Reed Film Corp., New Haven, CT, Panoramic group portrait, New Haven High School (in Series I), 1930 (Box 75)
  - Photos by Leonard Parke, Orlando, FL, Panoramic portrait group of Battery 'A', 76th Coast Artillery (in Series I), 1948 (Box 76)
  - The Elite Studio, New Haven, CT, Panoramic portrait: students and teachers of New Haven High School (in Series I), 1923 (Box 77)
  - Box number not used (Box 78)
  - Photographer? (covered label) "Absent But Not Forgotten" (in Series I), circa 1869 (Box 79)
  - Unknown photographer, Double bust length portraits of a couple (in Series I), circa 1915 (Box 80)
  - American Art Company, Portrait of a young woman, three quarter length seated (in Series I), circa 1895 (Box 81)
  - Unknown artist, Three quarter length informal portrait, lady standing in garden wearing white dress (in Series I), circa 1900 (Box 82)
  - Unknown photographer, Bust length portrait of a lady wearing a feathered hat (in Series I), circa 1890 (Box 83)
  - Unknown photographer, Bust length portrait of a lady in lace blouse (in Series I), circa 1910 (Box 84)
  - Unknown photographer, Oval bust length portrait of a lady with gold jewelry (in Series I), circa 1890 (Box 85)
  - Drawn by A. Henning, engraved by H.B. Hall, "Mount Vernon in Olden Time..." (in Series I), 1856 (Box 86)
  - E. Herline, Lith., Phila., "President Lincoln and His Cabinet..." (in Series I), circa 1864 (Box 87)
  - Del. Lith. and Print. by L. Lipman, Milwaukee, WI, Emancipation Proclamation; text in oval in center surrounded by 11 vignettes (in Series I), 1864 (Box 88)
  - Sunday News photo, "Joe Louis and John Henry Lewis, Challenger" (in Series I), 1939 (Box 89)
  - Pillow cover, "The Cakewalk" (in Series III), 1899 (Box 90)
  - Silkscreen, Tuskegee souvenir, Vignettes of Lincoln, Frederick Douglass, Booker T. Washington (in Series III), circa 1885 (Box 91)
  - Unknown photographer, Panoramic regimental group portrait of "'E' Company" (in Series I), 1956 (Box 92)
  - Weber, New Haven, CT, New Haven High School, Class of 1918 (in Series I) (Box 93)
  - Civil War service record, presented 1915, framed (in Series II) (Box 94)
  - "The U.S.S. Little, Officers and Crew." Early 20th century photograph (in Series I), undated (Box Broadside 95)
  - "The Pic-Nic on the Fourth of July" Engraving (mezzotint?) (in Series I), 1865 (Box Broadside 96)
  - "The First Reading of the Emancipation Proclamation before the Cabinet", engraving (in Series I), 1864 (Box Broadside 97)
  - Elderly man stands in barn doorway holding a white child, etching (in Series I), 1882 (Box Broadside 98)
  - Broadside for "12th Annual Tour of the Original Norfolk Jubilee Singers;" woodcut (in Series I), 1870s (Box Broadside 99)
  - "Callender's Famous Georgia Minstrels," advertisement broadside (in Series I), 1875 (Box Broadside 99)
  - E.G. Renesch, "Eight Illinois Regiment, now in France" (in Series I), 1918 (Box 100 (art))
  - Attributed to Charles Ethan Porter, Still Life of Vase of Chrysanthemums (in Series I), circa 1885 (Box 101 (art))
  - Unknown artist, Half length seated portrait of Frederick Douglass (in Series I), circa 1890 (Box 102 (art))
  - Unknown artist, Woman and her son in a train or bus station (in Series I), circa 1930 (Box 103 (art))
  - H. C. Wolcott, Bust length portrait of young woman (in Series I), undated (Box 104 (art))